快点  不能偷看
Come on, no peeking.
我们要闭眼睛过马路  太好了
Our eyes are closed, and we're crossing the street. Very good.
好  可以睁开了
Okay. Open up!
你们是要我们看什么
What do you want to show us?
我只看到  超炫的厢型车
Because all I can see is this bitchin' van!
这是我们做宴会的专用车
It's for our catering business.
我好像认识那女孩
I think I know that girl.
好啦  我们不会让它一直那样的
All right,we're not gonna really keep it this way though.
不会吗
No?
不会  我们会把宝刀换成法国面包
No, we're gonna paint over the sword, and replace it with a baguette.
还有这个也不知道要怎么处理
And also, we don't know what to do with this.
对  我一定认识她
Oh yeah, I definitely know her.
还记得我说过那个在烹饪学校
Remember that guy from cooking school I told you about
煮什么都加香菜的人吗
that put cilantro with everything?
记得  香菜赖瑞嘛
Sure, Cilantro Larry!
我要替他代班
Well, I'm gonna fill in for him
帮切尔西报道做美食评鉴
as food critic for the Chelsea Reporter.
莫妮卡  这可是大好机会呢  你能影响到
Wow, Monica! What an amazing opportunity to influence...
二  三十个人呢
dozens of people.
你居然同意了  那我们的宴会生意怎么办
How could you say yes, what about our catering business?
没关系的  只是每周一晚而已
Oh no-no-no, it's only one night a week,
而且我还可以带你们大家去吃免费晚餐
Plus I get to take all of you out for a lot of free dinners.
那样的话
Well, in that case
我刚才是表示赞同
That was me, hopping on board.
大伙儿好  罗斯
Hey, guys. Hey, Ross!
快问快答
Quick question for you.
你准备好要狂欢没
Are you ready to party?
不知道  出去喝几杯啤酒或许行
I don't know, I could maybe go out for a couple of beers,
但是今晚探索频道要演蜜蜂的节目
but there's this thing about bumblebees on The Discovery Channel...
你可能没听清楚
I don't think you heard me. are you ready...
你准备好要  狂欢没
...to party?
不会吧
No.
甘道夫吗  甘道夫来这里了吗
Gandalf? gandalf is coming to town?
反正凯西跟父母在一起  我没事干
Kathy's with her parents, I have nothing to do,
明天我们去跟甘道夫狂欢吧  伙计
So tomorrow we are partying with Gandolf dude!
兄弟  我们要去狂欢了耶
Dude, we are sooo gonna party!
好吧  兄弟请注意
Wow, okay. Dude alert!
这个人是谁
Who is this guy?
麦克·"甘道夫"·甘德森
Mike "gandalf" ganderson.
世界上最爆笑的人
only the funnest guy in the world.
我要打电话给公司  说明天请假
I'll call to get off work tomorrow.
你打完换我
I'll call after you!
兄弟  这一定超酷的
This will be so cool!
我们八百年没狂欢过
Dude, We never party anymore.
你们是不是躲在我们送货车里偷抽了大麻了
Were you smoking something in the back of our van?
记不记得去看脱衣舞那回
"we never have fun anymore"?
跟我在一起就很乐啊
you have fun with me.
还记得那些脱衣舞娘吗
Remember those strippers? and you
你们给我50美元要我吞书
paid me $50 to  him "gandalf"
乔伊  你一定会喜欢这个人
You are going to love this guy.
甘道夫是狂欢魔法师喔
gandalf is the party wizard.
你们干嘛叫他  甘道夫
Why do you call him "gandalf"?
巫师甘道夫啊
Gandalf the Wizard.
你高中时没看过指环王吗
Didn't you read lord of the rings in high school?
没  但我高中时有上过床
No, i had sex in high school.
乔安娜  有件事想请问一下
Joanna? i was wondering if i could ask you something.
小淑女服饰的采购助理有空缺
There's an opening for a buyer in junior miss
那我岂不是降级了吗
that'd be a step down for me.
不是啦  我是毛遂自荐
actually, i meant for me.
招聘委员会每天都在面试
The hiring committee is meeting people all day and....
我很希望我能拒绝
Well, I wish I could say no,
但总不能让你永远当我助理吧
I guess you can't stay my assistant forever.
苏菲  你也是  但理由不同
Neither can you, Sophie, but for different reasons.
真高兴你完全没有意见
God, I am so glad you don't have a problem with this,
否则我压根不会想去报考
Because if you did, I wouldn't even consider applying.
真的啊  那样的话
Really? Well, in that case…
所以你没意见  我很高兴
and that's I'm so glad  there's no problem.
没关系  其实我也是面试人员
That's fine; actually I'm on the hiring committee,
你起码能看到一张友善的脸
so there'll be at least one friendly face.
这真是太棒了
That's great!
我也是从小淑女部起家的
Junior miss is where i started.
为了得到那份工作  我跟一个丑男上床
I slept with the ugliest guy to get that job.
-这样啊  -开玩笑的啦
-really? -no.
真的
Yeah.
没有啦  假的假的
I mean, no.
别担心  以你的资历
Don't you worry, I'm sure with your qualifications
不用出卖肉体也能被录取
you won't need to sleep with some guyto get that job.
虽然我是不太相信
Although, I might need some convincing.
逗你的啦
Kidding!
天啊  我今天真亢奋
God, I feel wild today!
要命  我兴奋到都快吐了
Oh man! I am so excited-I may vomit!
你兴奋个什么劲  他不过就是个人嘛
Will you calm down? He's just a human guy.
你有所不知了  甘道夫超神的
Look you don't understand, Gandolf is amazing.
跟他出去可是惊喜连连
You know you're never know what's gonna end up happening,
你开始只不过是跟他去喝两杯
You go out for a couple of beers
醒来却发现躺在
and end up on
加拿大的新斯科舍省的一条渔船上
a fishing boat to Nova Scotia!
-真的吗  -对  那里风景很美
- Really? - It's beautiful country up there.
好了
Hey. okay.
我带了护照  干净的袜子  还有蛇毒解药
I got my passport, fresh socks, and a snakebite kit.
这次不会跟上次完全一样啦
It won't be exactly like last time.
回头见了
I'll see you guys.
我要先去试镜  晚点一定去跟你们会合
I have an audition, but I'll definitely hook up with you later.
你们中午会在哪里
Where will you be around noon?
差不多在赤道附近吧
Somewhere maybe along the equator?
你好
Hello?
甘道夫打来的
It's Gandalf!
你已经到了吗
So are you in town?
那就下次再约吧
Maybe next time, then.
怎么了
What happened?
他在芝加哥耽搁  没办法来
It's not gonna make it. He's stuck in Chicago.
天啊
Oh, man!
芝加哥真是太走运了
Chicago's so lucky.
我还蠢得去换这些没有用的加币
Stupid, useless. . .Canadian money!
格林小姐  你的履历让人印象深刻
You have a very impressive resume, Ms. Green.
我尤其喜欢这一段
I especially like what I see about
"实施档案管理系统"
implementing a new filing system.
谢谢
Thank you.
"档案管理系统"
Filing system?
你说资料夹上黏的彩色标签吗
You mean those-those little colored labels you put on allthe folders?
那的确是让档案柜生色不少
It certainly did brighten up the inside of the filing cabinets.
标签的功能不只是那样而已
Well, they uh, they-they do more than that.
我看到你肩负了许多重要职责
I notice that you've been trusted with a lot of rather important responsibilities.
对  乔安娜确实是对我有知遇之恩
Joanna really has been an incredible mentor to me.
每天早上给我送百吉饼
And Rachel has been really incredible
瑞秋确实做得非常不错
in getting my morning bagel for me.
更惊人的是  她每次都不会买错
It's amazing how she gets it right almost every time!
我的职责当然不止那样
Of course, I have more responsibilities than that.
没错  还有买咖啡
Of course! There's the coffee too.
瑞秋一次能拎两样东西
Rachel can carry two things at once.
这很好啊
That's very good.
这项工作的一大重点是
Now a big part of this job is
打好私人关系  尤其是和设计师
cultivating personalrelationships, especially with designers.
-对  我知道... -这一点瑞秋没问题
- Yes, I realize that... - And Rachel shouldn't have any problem with that.
只怕她打得太火热  你懂的我的意思吧
The only problem might be getting a little too friendly, if you know what I mean.
我最爱和设计师共事了
I love working with designers.
共事或共枕又有何差别呢  瑞秋
With them, under them, what's the difference? Eh, Rach
我第一篇美食评论出版了
My first review is out.
切尔西报道
The Chelsea Reporter.
我流浪的时候常拿它来盖在身上御寒
These used to keep me so warm.
快看  我写的刊在反面
Look, I'm on the back page.
我还会再光顾亚利山多洛斯餐厅吗
"Would I go back to Allesandro's?
当然  但我会点两份餐
Sure, but I'd get two meals.
一份给自己  一份给拿枪抵着我的人
One for me, and one for the guy pointing the gun to my head. "
你真把这家店批得一文不值
You really laid into this place.
报社付我钱  可不是要我广结善缘的
They don't pay me a penny a word to make friends.
我得走了  我找到一个可以修咱们货车的人
Ooh, I gotta go I found a guy who'd fix up the van for catering.
要我一起去吗
You want me to go?
不用了  没关系
It's okay.
但你确定我们不要那张水床吗
are we sure we don't want the waterbed?
我们不是早就说好了
Haven't we made this decision?
对啦  算了
Yeah, all right.
-再见  -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
谁啊
Who is it?
亚利山多洛斯的老板  亚利山多洛斯
it's allesandro, from allesandro's.
我的天啊  -我要跟你讨论美食评鉴的事
-Oh my God! -i want to talk to you about your review.
打电话给我吧
Call me on the phone.
好  让你挂我电话
What? So you can hang up on me?
我不会让你上来的  你还是走吧
I-I'm never gonna let you up so you may as well just go away.
给我一个机会  你要进来吗  请进
Just give me a chance to hey, do you need to get in? Here you go.
菲比  不行啦
No, Phoebe!
莫妮卡
Hey, Monica!
我要你收回你的话
I want a retraction.
我们的食物绝非  难以下咽
Our food is not "inedible swill. "
我就吃不下去
I couldn't eat it.
我那五个朋友也难以下咽
My five friends couldn't eat it,
其中一个人连书都吃
and one of them eats books.
我们的服务  也不是  完全无能
Our service isn't "grossly incompetent. "
侍者把面包棒塞在裤子里
The waiter carried the breadsticks in his pants.
你还写说  我们店里接受信用卡
Well, you said that we accept the Discover Card
我们其实没有
. . .which we do not!
好啊  那段话我可以收回
All right, that I'll retract.
但我坚持我的观点
But i stand by my review.
我知道怎么做菜  但决不是你们那样
i know food, and that wasn't it.
你们的大蒜番茄酱  简直跟番茄汁没两样
Your marinara is like tomato juice.
应该要配伏特加和芹菜茎
You should serve it with vodka and apiece of celery.
我以店里那酱汁为荣  美味极了
I'm proud of that sauce. It's delicious.
你是开意大利餐厅的
You own an Italian restaurant
竟然觉得那样叫做美味
and you think that tastes good?!
你到底是哪里人
Where are you from?
黎巴嫩
Lebanon.
把那些番茄给我
Hand me those tomatoes.
我来示范纯正的味道是怎样
I'll show you what it should taste like.
来  把那些递给我
Come on, hand me them.
你要弄多久  我还要去骂另一个美食评论家
How long will this take? i got another critic to yell at.
乔安娜  我要谈谈面试的事
Joanna, i want to talk about that interview.
我觉得你在面试中表现得很棒
I thought it went very well.
不  才怪  我就是要跟你说这件事
No, it didn't. that's what i want to talk to you about.
我先声明一句
Now just to brief you...
我可能会哭出来
...i may cry.
但那不是悲伤或气愤的泪水
But they are not tears of sadness or of anger...
只是因为我要跟你讨论这件事
...but just of us having this discussion.
瑞秋  麻烦你别丢人现眼了
Please, don't make a scene.
这里又没人
There's nobody here.
苏菲  你进来
Sophie, get in here.
看吧  你让苏菲尴尬了
See? you're making sophie uncomfortable.
她没有让我尴尬啊
She's not making me uncomfortable.
你刚证明了自己一无用处  滚吧
you crossed the line into completely uasional drink...
为什么  你怎么会这样想
Why? What makes you think that?
因为你在面试时讲的那些话
Well, of those things that you said in the interview,
如果里面有你的真心话
I mean if you believe any of them,
那我一定不是个好助理
I must not be a very good assistant.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我要来收拾办公桌
I am just going to pack up my desk
我等今天下班就走人
...and i will be gone by the end of the day.
我想没必要耗到今天下班了
There's no use staying till the end of the day.
你等等  等等
Wait, wait.
把那可怜的松糕放回抽屉里
You can put your sad little muffin back in its drawer.
如果你要听实话的话
If you must know the truth,
是我不想失去你这完美的助理
I didn't want to lose a perfectly good assistant.
什么
What?
这就是为什么我说你
That's why I said those things about your flirting and drinking.
轻浮和酗酒
about your flirting and drinking.
我酗酒
My drinking?
我等你离开之后才说的
I must have said that after you left.
你到底说了什么
Said what, exactly?
你三不五时喜欢喝一杯
You enjoy the occasional drink
然后酒后乱性
. . .-ing binge.
天啊  真是够了  我走人
Oh, my God! That is it. I'm leaving!
你这个人真的很糟糕
You are just a horrible person!
等等  等等  等等
Wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait-wait!!
如果你反应一定要这么激烈的话
If you're going to get all sensitive about it.
老实说  我不想失去你
I don't want to lose you.
不如我为你独家创造个职位
What if I create a position for you?
我让你在这个部门里  担任采购助理
I'll make you assistant buyer in this department.
你再多说一点
Say more things like that.
自己的办公室  外带加薪  明天就生效
Your own office and a raise, effective tomorrow.
-我需要公关费  -没问题
- I need an expense account. - Done!
-还要有助理  -苏菲  进来
- And an assistant. - Sophie, get in here!
你们怎么在这里
Hey! What are you guys doing here?
不是跟甘呆夫去狂欢了吗
I thought you'd be out partying with Gandel-worf.
是甘道夫  他不来了
It's Gandalf, and he's not coming.
那你们一早都呆坐在这里
So you've been sittin' around here all mornin'?
没有  我刚刚把我的支票算好了
No! I balanced my checkbook.
对  我给所有的足球桌里的小人都起了名字
Yeah, and I-I gave first names to all of the foosball players.
不敢相信甘道夫竟然没来
I can't believe he didn't come.
他不来又怎样  我们还是可以自己出去狂欢啊
So what if he didn't come!  We can still go out and party ourselves.
跟甘道夫一起  我们可以彻夜狂欢
Oh-no, you know with Gandolf we'd be out all night!
对啊  我们会跟刚认识的陌生人  一起玩
Yeah! We'd meet total strangers, and hang out with them!
我们也可以啊
We could do that.
他还有其他的绝招啦
There was other stuff too.
我们一网打尽  更胜于蓝
We'll do it all and better!
今晚过后  就换我们带甘道夫去狂欢
After tonight, Gandalf will want to party with us,
伙计  动起来
Dude, come on!
好像我们不会狂欢似的
As if we don't know how to party!
好  咱们走
All right! Let's go.
-最后再到一次船上如何  -好啊
- Maybe we could end up on a boat again? - All right!
上次在船上是何时
When were we on a boat?
还记得那天早上很冷
Remember that really cold morning,
一早醒来还有狗舔你的脸的那次吗
you woke up and those dogs werelicking your face?
-记得  -老兄  舔你的可是海豹呢
- Yeah. - Those were seals, man.
莫妮卡  快问快答
Hey Mon, little question for ya!
采购助理穿这套装如何
How would this suit look on an assistant buyer
亚利山多洛斯的老板上门来骂我
Okay, the owner of Allesandro's came over to yell at me,
但我乘势帮他做了酱料
but instead I made him some sauce,
结果他挖我去店里做主厨
and he offered me the job as head chef!!
天啊  你毁了我回家时练了一路的好戏
Oh my God!! You just ruined the thing I was practicing the whole way home,
但我真是替你高兴
but I'm so happy!
你相信吗  我终于可以拥有自己的厨房了
Can you believe it? i get to run my own kitchen!
你终于守得云开见月明了
Ohh, you've waited so long.
菲比  快问快答
Pheebs! Quick question for you.
鲁明戴尔的采购助理
How do you think this suit would look on
穿上这套装如何
. . .on an assistant buyer at Bloomingdale's?
我不知道  那完全要看她的肤色而定
I don't know, it would totally depend on her coloring and
你被录取啦
You got the job!
你被录取了怎么没跟我说
You got the job? Why didn't you tell me?
一定超棒的  我能帮忙决定要卖什么
It'll be so great! I'm gonna get to help decide what we sell,
还有全套装潢的私人办公室
I'll have an office with walls and everything.
四面都有墙耶
I'm going to have walls!
今天真是好消息连连  我帮咱俩接到活了
Is this the day of good news or what? i got us a job.
喜宴宴会
The wedding reception.
菲比  我有话要跟你说
I kind of need to talk to you about that.
我想宴会的事不能操之过急
Well I-I-I think it might be time for me to take a step back from catering.
但我们才刚做了一笔生意
But we've only had one job.
我知道  但现在有第二笔了
I know. But now we have this second one,
就像雪球越滚越大
and it feels like it's snowballing.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
亚利山多洛斯餐厅请我去当主厨
I got offered the head chef job at Allesandro's.
什么
What?
不碍事的  其实仔细想想
It's okay, 'cause y'know what? If you think about it,
你不是很需要我
You don't really need me for the business.
你是厨师啊
You're the cook!
总不能我自己一个开去别人家
Without you, it's just me driving up to people's houses...
带着空盘子就跟人要钱吧
...with empty trays, asking for money.
好  我会把你所有投资的钱都还给你
All right. but i'll pay you back all the money you invested.
-还有货车归你  -我要拿来干嘛
-and you can keep the van! -for what?
我真是不敢相信
I can't believe this!
我得离开这里
I got to get out of here.
菲比  你等等
Phoebe, wait a minute.
我升采购助理了
I'm an assistant buyer!
我们先喝咖啡养足精神  再重新出动
All right, so we'll get a little coffee, we'll get energized, and we'll head back out.
-好吧  -好
- Yeah, all right. - Okay.
很好玩嘛  对不对
So we're having fun, right?
我们才不需要那个什么魔法师
We don't need that wizard guy.
我们去了几家具乐部  跟一些陌生人说过话
We hit some clubs, talk to some strangers...
等一下去码头  安排坐船的事
...then go down to the docks and see about that boat thing.
我有点累了
I'm kind of beat.
其实
Actually...
我也是
...me too.
-你们是真的假的  -真的
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
感谢老天  我也累毙了
Thank God! I'm exhausted.
-你们要喝咖啡吗  -对
- You guys want coffees? - Yeah.
但我今天想早点睡  所以我要无咖啡因的
I don't want to be up too late, so I'll have a decaf.
对  我也是
Yeah, me too.
我能来杯热水加点柠檬汁吗
Actually, can I get some hot water with a little lemon?
我刚才在那家店里都喊到哑了
I strained my voice screaming in there.
他们音乐非要开那么大声吗
Does it have to be so loud?
我听不到你说什么  我耳鸣得厉害
I can't hear what you said. My ears are ringing so bad.
幸好我多带了一双袜子
I'm just glad I brought that extra pair of socks, y'know?
拿来当手套用
I used them as mittens.
最后那家店的任何东西  我都不敢用手碰
I didn't want to touch a thing in that last place.
我们真是可悲到了极点
How sad are we?
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
其实我们并不可悲
You know what? We're not sad
只是我们都过了21岁
We're just not 21 anymore. You know?
靠  我都已经29岁了
I'm 29 years old, damm it!
只想舒服地坐着看电视
And I want to sit in a comfortable chair, and watch television
时间到了就上床睡觉
and go to bed at areasonable hour!
我喜欢去安静一点的地方
I like to hang out in a quiet place
-才能好好跟朋友聊天  -对啊
- where I can talk to my friends.- Yeah.
就算回家听肯尼基的音乐洗澡
And so what if I like to go home,
又有什么大不了
throw on some Kenny G, and take a bath!
我们是29岁没错  但我们可不是娘儿们
We're 29. We're not women
你到了
There you are.
我很高兴你决定听我解释
I'm glad you decided to hear me out.
好  你说吧
Okay, I'm hearing.
我想了很多  很多很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking. A lot.
而且我想出了一堆
And umm, well, I came up with a whole bunch of businesses
你能用上你货车的事业
that you can do with your van. Okay?
-你可以去送花  -什么
- You could be a flower delivery person. - What?
或是送面包
Or a bakery delivery person?
送披萨
Pizza?
莫妮卡
Monica!
我写了一堆你能运送的东西
I got a whole bunch of stuff in this area.
但我有预感你不想送货
But I get the feeling you don't want to deliver.
-对  -那好吧
- No. - Okay.
我猜若你不想送货的话
I guess if you don't want to deliver
八成也不会想去载货
you probably don't want to pick up stuff either.
对
No.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我们来做宴会
Let's do the catering business.
-真的你确定  -对  我承诺过你
-really? are you sure? -yeah, i made a commitment to you.
会很有趣的
It'd be fun.
一定会很有趣的
It will be fun!
那我们来计划喜宴的事
Let's plan the wedding reception.
你还真是替我想了好多用那货车的办法呀
You really wanted me to do something with this van.
不如这样吧  我要你接下那主厨的工作
You know what? I want you to take the chef job.
-真的吗  -对
- Really? - Yeah.
那是你真心想要做的
That's what you really want.
我不想成为你不高兴的原因
I don't want to be the reason you're unhappy.
我最不想让自己不高兴了
And I really don't want to be the reason I'm unhappy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
而且成立新的特攻队  应该会很好玩
Besides, it might be kind of fun to form the new A-Team.
林奇太太  乔安娜进公司了吗
Hi, Mrs. Lynch. Is Joanna in already?
老天  你还没听说吗
Oh, my goodness! You haven't heard.
-听说什么  -乔安娜
-heard what? -joanna...
昨晚过世了
...passed away last night.
天啊  怎么会这样
Oh, my god! how?
她下班出去时被计程车撞上
She was leaving work, and she was hit by a cab.
天啊  我不敢相信
Oh, my god! i cannot believe it!
我知道
I know.
天啊
Oh, god. oh, god.
Oh, god.
没想到你们两个这么好
I didn't realize that you were so close.
对  好到不行
Yes. so close!
林奇太太  我知道这个节骨眼大家都很悲伤
Mrs. Lynch, I know that this is an emotional and difficult time  for all of us.
但在事发之前
But by any chance, did Joanna. . .
乔安娜是不是正好有
...send any paperwork your way before...
-把什么文件交给你  -什么都没有
-...it happened? -no, nothing.
只盼当初  她晚个几秒钟过街就没事了
Imagine, if she'd just stepped off that curb a few seconds later.
对  差个几秒钟  她就还能跟我们在一起
Yes-yes, just a few seconds and she'd still be with us.
她没说到采购助理的事
Nothing about an assistant buyer?
不好意思  我得走了
I'm sorry. I have to go.
早安
Good morning!
苏菲  我猜你还不知道乔安娜的事
Oh, Sophie, I guess you didn't hear about Joanna
我当然知道
I sure did!
我很兴奋能请到莫妮卡加入
I'm excited about having Monica on board with us.
虽然开除艾米里欧主厨 让我觉得很过意不去
Although I do feel bad about having fired Chef Emilio.
那就像是失去了一个家人
It is like losing a member of the family.
不过  对其中几位而言  真的是失去家人
Of course, that literally is the case for several of you.
东尼  卡洛斯  玛莉
Tony, carlos, marie...
请向你们的父亲转达我们的思念
...please tell your father how much we're going to miss him.
我知道莫妮卡对这家店  有许多很棒的点子
I know monica has a lot of great ideas for this place.
你们都看过她那篇评论了
Well, you all read the review.
所以废话不多说
So without much further ado...
在此向各位介绍本店的新主厨
...I present to you our new head chef.
我只想说只要有热忱
I just want to say that with a pinch of excitement...
肯吃苦  肯合作
...a dash of hard work and a dollop of cooperation...
我们就能将本店的菜色
...we can have the recipe....
你们打算宰了我吗
Are you going to kill me?